ACTWU Labor Unity Photograph Files 5981 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: LABOR UNITY
  - Sewing Machine Operators., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff160 Includes: 1978 "Garment Industry Occupations" newsletter.
  - Seymour, Edward., 1976 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff161 Includes: portrait 1976.
  - Shanberg, Louise., 1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff162 Includes: April 1988, Louise Shanberg and Susan Bolles; Shanberg with organizers and kids during 1930s organizing drive, Springfield, Mass.; contact sheet.
  - Sheinkman and Finley (together)., 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff163 Includes: group shots; contact sheet; with Tailored Clothing negotiating committee; at General EB meeting, Bal Harbour, FL 3/77; 1976; speeches; clothing workers get official visit; Finley, Meany, Sheinkman; to
  - Sheinkman and Finley (together)., 1976 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff164 Includes: group shots; 1976; PR clothing workers get official visit; Sallee, Finley, Sheinkman; march; with painting; contact sheet.
  - Sheinkman and Finley (together)., 1972-1981 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff165 Includes: contact sheets; 12/5/72 Labor News Conference, AFL-CIO radio show, Sheinkman, Lloyd Schwartz, Don Finley; Workman's Circle Home and Infirmary, speech; Sheinkman speech, 1981 convention; 10/77 Sheinkma
  - Sheinkman and Finley (together)., 1979-1985 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff166 Includes: Senate Labor Subcommittee, John Sweeney, Sheinkman; Senate Labor hearings, Elizabeth Smith, Sheinkman, Eric Frumin; GEB; press briefing, Jacob Sheinkman, Wilbur Daniels, Donald Dekieffer, Morton Coope
  - Sheinkman and Finley (together)., 1978-1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff167 Includes: Sheinkman on the air; swearing in NYJB 2/82; Sheinkman at 1978 Stevens boycott; press conference: Sheinkman, Prof. Ginsberg, Mario Biaggi, William Green; Jack at NCSC gathering in Washington DC 7/22/8
  - Sheinkman and Finley (together)., 1987 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff168 includes: 6/22/87 PAI; testifies before Senate panel, Sheinkman, Sweeney, Mazur; testifying before House subcommittee on Trade, Sheinkman, Thomas Roboz, Robert Laidlaw, Lloyd Cline; Victory, Convention 6/87; Sh
  - Sheinkman in Baltimore.: (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff169 Includes: group shots; playing "UNO" with children; shaking hands; audience; on television; in meeting; with child dressed as robot; meeting at high school, Chambersburg, PA with Baltimore Regional JB; Baltimor
  - Sheinkman in El Paso.: (Box 31, Folder 11)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff170 Includes: outside Levi's; with reporters; group shots; meetings; band; shop floor.
  - Sheinkman in El Paso 7/83., 1983 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff171 Includes: Bishop Sidney M. Metzger; Sheinkman at meetings; Sheinkman meets workers.
  - Sheinkman in Maryland.: (Box 31, Folder 13)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff172 Includes: Sheinkman visits L. 107 at Rob Roy, Cambridge, MD; workers; Sheinkman tour of plants.
  - Sheinkman in Philadelphia.: (Box 31, Folder 14)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff173 Includes: Sheinkman, informal lunch w/ editors of Philadelphia Inquirer; Sheinkman, installation Philadelphia Clothing Joint Board; Freeman worker greets Sheinkman, John Fox, Nicholas DiPierno; tour through Sta
  - Sheinkman in Rochester, NY, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff174 Includes: Sheinkman at Hickey- Freeman, Rochester; Sheinkman visits New England plants.
  - Sheinkman, Ital-Amer Award, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b7, ff175 Includes: contact sheets.
  - Sheinkman Missouri Tour 5/84., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Includes: meetings; plant tours; demonstrations of tasks; speech; millinery shop; headquarters Southwest Regional Joint Board; lunch break at California Manufacturing Co.; hats; contacts sheets; Wee Walker shoe plant.
  - Sheinkman Tennessee Tour. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Includes: meetings; plant tours; "Made in USA" label; group shots; Tennford Weaving; Palm Beach; dinner; contact sheets.
  - Sheinkman Testifies in Wash. DC 4/87., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Includes: Eric Frumin, Jack Sheinkman, David Mallino testify before Health/Safety subcommittee, 3/26/87; William Wynn, James E. Hatfield, Sheinkman, Milan Stone, testify.
  - Sheinkman Tours 4 Maine Cities 8/83., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Includes: Visiting shops.
  - Sheinkman Tours 4 South Texas Apparel Plants 4/83., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Includes: Group shots; shop tours.
  - Sheinkman Visit El Salvador/Nicaragua 7/85., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Includes: photocopies of photos of visit; children.
  - Sheinkman Visits Massachusetts Apparel, Textile, & Shoe Plants. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Includes: Shop tours; meetings; talking to reporters; contact sheet.
  - Sheinkman Visits New England Plants 3/83., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Includes: Shop tours; meetings; talking to reporters; contact sheets.
  - Sheinkman Visits New Jersey Shops 5/83., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Includes: Clifton Clothes, NJ; Danny Boy, Eliz, NJ; Northern Feather; Kalirstern Silk Mills; Garylin Togs, NJ; shop tours; meetings; contact sheets.
  - Sheinkman Visits New York Shops 12/82., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Includes: Shop tours; greeting workers; group shots.
  - Sheinkman Visits Scranton Wilkes-Barre 11/83., 1983 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Includes: Radio interview; with media reporters in background, Sheinkman discusses union situation; in clothing plant Adrian DeMarco, Ted Gatto, Henry Dropkin, Nicholas Stefano; co. Lunchroom meal; getting orders ready for shipment; "Made in the USA" la
  - Sheinkman Visits West Coast 11/82. [folder 1 of 2], 1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Includes: contact sheets, photocopies of Sheinkman tour shots; at Kudovgoski; at Xerox; meetings; speeches; negatives; plant tours; at Chase Bay; group shots; at Selwood; in S. California; reviewing documents with California Joint Board Business Agent a
  - Sheinkman Visits West Coast 11/82. [folder 2 of 2], 1982 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Includes: contact sheets, photocopies of Sheinkman tour shots; at Kudovgoski; at Xerox; meetings; speeches; negatives; plant tours; at Chase Bay; group shots; at Selwood; in S. California; reviewing documents with California Joint Board Business Agent and
  - Sheinkman West, Central PA Hoyman. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Includes: tour, Avtex; with L.8T; with L.1099, K & B Sportswear Phillipsburg, PA; with L.118C Kent Shop Curwensville, PA; in Target Fletcherville Plant, Clearfield, PA cutting room, steward's family; at Eaglewear, Galletyn, PA, Sheinkman and Dropkin with
  - Shell Boycott. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Includes: Demonstration outside Blake Building.
  - Sherman, Ed/Penna. Keystone Joint Board. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Includes: Joseph Coponi, Preston Stockel, Sherman, Joseph Kravitz, Joe Rudolph, Wayne Martz, Charles Long; contact sheet.
  - Shindler, Samuel. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Ships., 1945 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Includes: Penmar; Polish ship; Harrison Cargo Gear at Baltimore SS Sea Hawk, unloading crude sugar at American Sugar Refineries plant, 2/23/45.
  - Shipyard Workers. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Includes: Ship workers.
  - Shirt and Leisurewear., 1973-1989 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Includes: Liz Claiborne Assoc. Organizing committee; Liz Claiborne in-plant committee; "English" Graduation class, 10/17/85, Shirt and Leisurewear headquarters, NY; May "English " class; Shirt and Leisurewear Joint Board; March of Dimes Walkathon Winners,
  - Shirt and Leisurewear Jt. Bd. Xmas Party., 1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Includes: 1985 Xmas party; group shot with tree; contact sheet.
  - Shoaff, James. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Includes: Tribute to Shoaff, luncheon, NYS Americana Hotel: Bernard Ferster, Mrs. Shoaff, Chester Kessler, Robert Dale, Murray Finley, Jack Sheinkman; contact sheet.
  - Shoe Division., 1978-1984 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Includes: woman; testimony, Arthur Gundersheim and Diane Walker, Jeanne Hebert of Maine Shoe workers Organizing Committees; shoe conference Wash, DC 1/82; Shoe Division Council; NY Shoe Div. Officer Installation 1984; class, Kitchener, Ontario; Shoe worke
  - Shoe Division Conference LU 1/82., 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    Includes: Shoe Div. Conference in Wash, DC Dec. 1981: De Novelis, Georgian, Sheinkman; Contact sheets, 12/16/81 awards dinner and reception, Capitol Hilton, Washington, DC.
  - Shoe Division Convention., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Includes: NBU Shoe workers Convention, 2/79; speeches; group shots.
  - Shoe Division Joint Council 13. (Box 8, Folder 26)
    Includes: L.563 Shoe Service Union swearing in; Joint Council 13 group shots; contact sheet.
  - Shoe Imports. (Box 8, Folder 27)
    Includes: International Trade commission hearings on footwear imports: Finley, Angelo Georgian, John Mara, Art Gundersheim, Rudy Oswald, Lane Kirkland.
  - Shoe Manufacturers Council., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    Includes: 1/24/84 contact sheet, Shoe Manufacturers Council Press Conference.
  - Shoe Workers Attend Classes on Education. (Box 8, Folder 29)
    Includes: School for Shoe locals- Sarcoxie, MD.
  - Shop Talk., 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    Includes: Odell Underhill and James Anderson; L.2351; January 1981 shop talk; Columbus, GA February 1980; Fieldcrest, Columbus, Ga., L.1855 February 1980 shop talk; contact sheet L.1855 Fieldcrest Plant, Columbus and Sylvester, GA; L.1855 weave room stewa
  - Shore, Dinah., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    Includes: photocopies of NY Times 11/17/77; Shore displays new line of designer sheets for JP Stevens; letter from JP Stevens Support Committee to Dinah Shore; child protests appearance of Dinah Shore in Cincinnati, outside Stouffer's.
  - Siegel, Lewis and Wife. (Box 8, Folder 32)
    Includes: couple display pins; close-up of "Convict No. 2253 For President" pin.
  - Silkwood, Karen. (Box 8, Folder 33)
    Includes: woman, victim nuclear conspiracy.
  - Simon, Louis/Scholarships. [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Includes: contact sheets, Louis Simon, Cecil Toppin, Leo Kerness; Simon at Convention; biography; Simon honored by National Urban League; Louis Simon Scholarship Awards 1979; Louis Simon, 1976, presenting award; Simon addresses scholarship winners.
  - Simon, Louis/Scholarships. [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Simon, Paul Rep. Ill.. (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Skurjat, Victor. (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Includes: appreciation ceremony; Vic Skujat, Charles "Bud" Clark, NDP Convention.
  - Smart Money. (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Includes: brown bag lunch; cartoon of meat prices; two eggs in a pan.
  - Smith, Liz. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 39 Includes: speech; Smith at microphone; Smith at desk; with Garry Studd (D-Mass); at table; contact sheets; GEB meeting; Charles Brain, James Shannon (D-Mass), Smith; with Stetin; addressing Upper South Region an
  - Smithsonian Exhibition., 1976-1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 40 Includes: Smithsonian 11/86 exhibit; Smithsonian Institution, Festival of American Folklife, Working American Exhibit, August 1976; L.125 woman demonstrates making Gant shirts, Smithsonian Institution, Festival
  - Smokeout, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 41 Includes: Smokeout 1986:Florence Lynch, Richard Perspirica, Ed James; graduation from behavior modification program; Sidney Hillman Center, Samuel Schecters takes a breathing test, Great American Smokeout table
  - Sneed, Geneva. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 42 Includes: Southeastern Clothing Regional Board, Knoxville, Tennessee group shot.
  - Snider, Ed. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 43 Includes: photocopies.
  - Social Democrats. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 44 Includes: Social Democrats, USA speech; Social Democrats USA conversing; contact sheets.
  - Social Services Conference (Allentown, Pa.), 1980 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 45 Includes: 1980 bus; conference in PA group shot; contact sheets; Allentown Social Services Conference Joint Board Managers, Kopach, Coponi, Mauro DeFazio, Sam Carita, Ruth Antoniades; meeting at Allentown Social
  - Social Services Council Formed in Missouri LU 1983 9/83. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 46 Includes: Cape Giradeau Social Services Conference 9/83 contact sheets; Cape Giradeau, Mo. Meeting, L.1106 and Council of Community Agencies.
  - Social Services- Humanities- Daycare- Health- Etc., 1980 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 47 Includes: Social Services, 12/80 group with certificates; NBU Daycare, enthralled boy; (Black) girl on playground.
  - Social Services Mobile Office (NC). (Box 32, Folder 10)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 48 Includes: List of hospitals with Hill-Burton Act funds, Social Services committee.
  - Solar Energy. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 49 Includes: Drawing of sun; George Whetstone, with two old radiators hooked together.
  - Solarz, Steve. (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 50 Includes: Contacts sheets; portrait; Override the Veto Demo, NY Joint Board and ACTWU shoe workers, with union retirees stand outside Solarz's Brooklyn offices.
  - Song of the Canary. (Box 32, Folder 13)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 51 Includes: Empty.
  - South Carolina- AFL-CIO. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 52 Includes: Group shots; contact sheet.
  - South Jersey Joint Board. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 53 Includes: Olympic weight set donated to YMCA, Michael Oliva, Mark Ruskoski.
  - Southeast Clothing Joint Board., 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 54 Includes: Bruce Raynor, Garry Ferraris, James Barnhart, Albert Gore, Geneva Sneed; installation ceremonies in Knoxville, Tennessee, Kentucky, Alabama, and East Tennessee locals; Dave Macon, Geneva Sneed, Emma Da
  - Southern California Joint Board., 1976-1982 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 55 Includes: Raymond Marin; nine unemployed members of California Joint Board, "Hunger in America" hearing, LA; Leaders Conference 1/23/82; 1982 Scholarship Awards recipients; West Coast scholarship recipients; Leo
  - Southern California Joint Board Story, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 56 Includes: 7/80 worker; 7/80 group shot, workers; retail, LA 7/80; Zody's Claussen Avenue store; pressers; (Hispanic) workers; 7/80 Southern California Joint Board contact sheets.
  - Southern Cookbook-Geraldine Ramsey. (Box 32, Folder 19)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 57 Includes: Ramsey with cookbook.
  - Southern Labor School (Wrightsville Beach, NC) (Box 32, Folder 20)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 58 Includes: Southern Labor class.
  - Southern New England Joint Board. (Box 32, Folder 21)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 59 Includes: Relief check, Local 121H member, Korber Hats, Fall River, Mass.
  - Southern Wage Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 60 Includes: 1981 Spartansburg, SC, Tom Turnip seed speaks, Scott Hoyman, James Johnson, James Walraven; L.1855 Southern Wage Drive, leafleting, Swift Spinning Mills Columbus, Ga.; 1980 Southern Wage Conference, Ho
  - Southern Wage Conference Greensboro, NC., 1979 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 61 Includes: delegates, textile workers from Carolinas, Alabama, Tennessee, and Virginia; contact sheet.
  - Southern Wage Conference- Columbia, SC (3/77)., 1977 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 62 Includes: Contact sheets; conference, Carolina Inn, 3/77; speeches; J.P. Stevens Workers, Wallace, NC; delegates.
  - Southern Wage Drive. (Box 32, Folder 25)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 63 Includes: Contact sheets; workers outside plant.
  - Southwestern Ontario Joint Board., 1983 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 64 Includes: Annual dinner and dance; officers elected; Local 1066 member gets $8000 indemnity; students at Southwest Ontario School; "Getting Organized Against Discrimination" school, Nov.8-13, Brantford; George C
  - Spiegel, Jack., 1982 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 65 Includes: 10/19/82 Audrey Miller, Jack Spiegel, Richard Stone, L.67 Nunn Bush Shoe Co. Edgerton, WI.
  - Spitzer, Leon., 1976 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 66 Includes: William C. Hall, Leon Spitzer, Murray Finley; Leon Spitzer at convention; head shot; at 1976 convention.
  - Springdale Mills (Valleyfield, Quebec). (Box 32, Folder 29)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 67 Includes: Women at table.
  - St. Louis Joint Board., 1978-1984 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 68 Includes: Summer 1978, Chas. Sallee speaking, Joint Board meeting; burns mortgage papers: Marsell Westbrook, James Boyer, Garold Rulon, Charles Sallee; Joint Board Textile Summer 1978; Stetin at Joint Board Meet
  - St. Louis Joint Board Health Center. (Box 32, Folder 31)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 69 Includes: Waiting room; dental clinic; trustees of St. Louis Employers- ACTWU Health Benefit Program Board Meeting: Francis Kern, Robert C. Riegel, Charles Sallee, Sherman Harmon, Dick Price, Lynn Miller; dispen
  - St. Louis Social Services Committee (Story). (Box 32, Folder 32)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 70 Includes: committee with Patricia Brandt; Brandt chats with committee member.
  - St. Louis Social Services Story 4/78., 1978 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 71 Includes: contact sheet.
  - St. Louis Staff Conference. (Box 32, Folder 34)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 72 Includes: Midwest Joint Board (Textile Division) and the Southwest Regional Joint Board meet in St. Louis.
  - St. Vincent De Paul Story. (Box 32, Folder 35)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 73 Includes: Contact sheet.
  - Standard Linen Co. (Box 32, Folder 36)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 74 Includes: Local 667 committee members, laundry workers, Standard Linen Co., Portland, ME.
  - Standard Products. (Box 32, Folder 37)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 75 Includes: Group shot.
  - Stanwood Mills, Slatington, PA. (Box 32, Folder 38)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 76 Includes: Workers meet to formulate demands; new local's negotiating committee.
  - Starr, Emil., 1953 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 77 Includes: Portrait, 9/53.
  - Steelworkers., 1981 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 78 Includes: Female steelworkers, 1981; Sudbury, Ontario check presented to Local 6500 Strike Fund to steelworkers.
  - Steelworkers Telecast-Support Committee., 1986 (Box 32, Folder 41)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 79 Includes: Support Committee for locked out USX workers: Lane Kirkland, Lynn Williams, Murray Finley, George Becker, Howard Samuel; ACTWU at Maryland Ribbon plant Hagerstown, MD during 6/21/86 Steelworkers' tele
  - Steenburgh, Tim. (Box 32, Folder 42)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 80 Includes: Man receives check.
  - Sterilization. (Box 32, Folder 43)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 81 Includes: Willow Island, West Virginia, January 4th, sterile women workers at American Cyanamid plant.
  - Sterlingwear. (Box 32, Folder 44)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 82 Includes: Woman working at Sterlingwear plant.
  - Stetin, Sol., 1976-1989 (Box 32, Folder 45)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 83 Includes: 10/89 head shot; 1981 speech; Cotton Dust testimony; GEB meeting; meeting with Ohio AFL-CIO leaders, with Warren Smith; Cleveland Boycott strategy luncheon; Stetin, Hoyman, and Perkel, 3/`6/78; Labor D
  - Stetin, Sol., 1975-1976 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 84 Includes: Dunton presents scroll to Stetin, Washington ceremony; Stetin, Oneita, 8/1976; discussing Burke-Hartke Bill: James Burke, Stetin, George Perkel, Bruce Dunton, Howard Samuel, Lazare Teper, hearing room
  - Stetin, Sol., 1971-1981 (Box 32, Folder 47)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 85 Includes: 1976 speech; 5/31/75 certificate from William Patterson College of New Jersey; 9/20/78 sworn in as trustee, William Patterson College, Fred Lafer; 1979 contact sheet; union presents $100,000 to Rutgers
  - Stetin, Sol., 1972-1989 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 86 Includes: Contact sheets; Stetin greets Newberry delegates outside Local 324 union hall; Stetin with porno calendar; portrait; Cotton Dust testimony; 10/89 Contact sheets; Stetin in Amsterdam ITGLWF Congress 10/
  - Stevens, Amanda. (Box 32, Folder 49)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 87 Includes: Portrait.
  - Stevenson. (Box 32, Folder 50)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 88 Includes: Adlai Stevenson '82 Campaign for Governor of Illinois; speech; at desk, as Senator of Illinois.
  - Stewart, Don (D-Alabama). (Box 32, Folder 51)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 89 Includes: Portraits.
  - Stickney, Illinois Health Service. (Box 32, Folder 52)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 90 Includes: Medical clinics.
  - Stinson, Corliss. (Box 32, Folder 53)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 91 Includes: Corliss and Andrea Stinson (Black).
  - Stock Exchange. (Box 32, Folder 54)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 92 Includes: Strike Local 153.
  - Stoneham and Rutters Laundry. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 93 Includes: Ed Clark shows vote tally.
  - Stop Smoking Sessions. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 94 Includes: Classes; patients.
  - Strikes/Marches 1199 CWA., 1989 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 95 Includes: 1199/CWA march 8/89 contact sheets; protest march 8/89.
  - Struggle for Justice in Schools Continues., 1961-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 96 Includes: Hamilton Holmes and Charlayne Hunter-Gault, first Black students to enter the University of Georgia in 1961, 1986; Hunter-Gault studying, 1960s.
  - Stulberg, Louis. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 97 Includes: Portrait.
  - Suarez, Joseph. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 98 Includes: San Antonio shots; Portrait; Joan Suarez with Lloyd Bentsen.
  - Sullentrup, James. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 99 Includes: Portrait.
  - Sullivan, Anna. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 100 Includes: Anna Sullivan, COPE director, Springfield, Mass.
  - Supermarkets-Consumer Prices. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Collection re-housed - formerly - b8, f 101 Includes: Man shopping; contact sheets.
  - Sutton, Crystal Lee., 1980 (Box 33, Folder 10)